Hello everyone, in this video, we are going to learn about this earth controller.js file
and how to use this one, okay.
So whatever the functions that we are getting here, so request response, rest.sense, sign
up page.
So we are going to import these functions inside of this earth.controller.js, okay.
So we are going to make, make use of that function like this export const, sign up equals
to what request and response.
So we are going to just cut copy these functions from here, okay.
So let us cut this, so cutting this function from here and then just paste these functions
here, okay.
In place of this, like this, similarly we are going to do with all of these like for this
login function, we are going to cut this from here and we are going to paste it here
in export const log in equals to the function and similarly after this, we are having
this logger function, okay.
So logger function just cut out from here, so cut it and now after cutting it, this paste
it here and store this in a variable, so export const log out, okay.
So export const log out equal to request response and reus.send.
So now these functions are content inside of this sign up sign login and log out variables,
okay.
So what we are going to do is just import this from this art controller.js, okay.
So import, so sign up login and log out, so sign up login comma log out.
So imported all of these from art.controller.js and we are going to just save it, there is
some issue with it, let me check it out.
So here actually we need to just use this sign up and then we are going to use this login
and then after that we are also going to use this log out, so log out.
So now let's try to run this one, so correctly server is running on the code 5000.
So what we have did here is that whatever the controllers, like whatever the functions we
have written for this sign up and log in and log out, we have just segregated into
rows in another file which is called as art controller.js, we have just made another set
of variables like sign up login and log out and then after storing the value of the functions
here, we have imported those in the author out.js and we have just set up with the route
get request, okay.
So sign up login and log out.
So in the next video what we are going to do is we are just going to work with our database
connectivity, okay.
So we are going to use the MongoDB database for our connections.